{
  "candidates": [
      {
        "id": "b5f2",
        "fullName": "Bhanu Pratap Singh",
        "email": "bhanusingh09@gmail.com",
        "password": "BhanuPS09"
      },
      {
        "id": "0fff",
        "fullName": "Manoj",
        "email": "manoj10@gmail.com",
        "password": "Manoj10"
      },
      {
        "id": "4457",
        "fullName": "Akshari",
        "email": "akshari10@gmail.com",
        "password": "Akshari10"
      },
      {
        "id": "1f51",
        "fullName": "Aniketh",
        "email": "aniketh10@gmail.com",
        "password": "Aniketh10"
      },
    ],
    "admins": [
      {
        "id": "864f",
        "fullName": "Admin",
        "email": "admin10@gmail.com",
        "password": "Admin10"
      }
    ],
    "instructors": [
      {
        "id": "4225",
        "fullName": "Instructor1",
        "email": "instructor01@gmail.com",
        "password": "Instructor10"
      },
      {
        "id": "6db2",
        "fullName": "Instructor2",
        "email": "instructor02@gmail.com",
        "password": "Instructor10"
      }
    ],
    "courses": [
    {
      "id": "5692",
      "courseId": "1",
      "name": "Angular Basics",
      "startDate": "2024-12-21",
      "endDate": "2024-12-28",
      "technology": "TypeScript",
      "status": "Upcoming",
      "instructor": "Sandeep"
    },
    {
      "id": "5693",
      "courseId": "2",
      "name": "React Basics",
      "startDate": "2024-12-21",
      "endDate": "2024-12-28",
      "technology": "JavaScript",
      "status": "Upcoming",
      "instructor": "Rabin"
    }
  ],
  "applicantDetails": [
    {
      "id": "703c",
      "fullName": "karna",
      "contactNumber": "08868817364",
      "email": "shekharjugtwan2002@gmail.com",
      "experience": 1,
      "teachingDomain": "Mathematics",
      "specialization": "Programming",
      "degree": "dfa",
      "certifications": "adsfadsf",
      "daysAvailable": "",
      "hoursAvailable": "",
      "resume": null
    },
    {
      "id": "e29d",
      "fullName": "shyam",
      "contactNumber": "08868817364",
      "email": "shekharjugtwan2002@gmail.com",
      "experience": 2,
      "teachingDomain": "Computer Science",
      "specialization": "Data Structures",
      "degree": "M Tech - CSE",
      "certifications": " SAP cloud computing",
      "daysAvailable": "45",
      "hoursAvailable": "1024",
      "resume": null
    },
    {
      "id": "ef31",
      "fullName": "",
      "contactNumber": "",
      "email": "",
      "experience": "",
      "teachingDomain": "",
      "specialization": "",
      "degree": "",
      "certifications": "",
      "daysAvailable": "",
      "hoursAvailable": "",
      "resume": null
    },
    {
      "id": "f9b2",
      "fullName": "karna",
      "contactNumber": "08868817364",
      "email": "shekharjugtwan2002@gmail.com",
      "experience": 1,
      "teachingDomain": "Mathematics",
      "specialization": "Programming",
      "degree": "dfa",
      "certifications": "adsfadsf",
      "daysAvailable": "",
      "hoursAvailable": "",
      "resume": null
    }
  ],
  "instructorDetails": [
    {
      "id": "703c",
      "fullName": "karna",
      "contactNumber": "08868817364",
      "email": "shekharjugtwan2002@gmail.com",
      "experience": 1,
      "teachingDomain": "Mathematics",
      "specialization": "Programming",
      "degree": "dfa",
      "certifications": "adsfadsf",
      "daysAvailable": "",
      "hoursAvailable": "",
      "resume": null
    },
    {
      "id": "2a4c",
      "fullName": "ram",
      "contactNumber": "08868817364",
      "email": "shekharjugtwan2002@gmail.com",
      "experience": 1,
      "teachingDomain": "Mathematics",
      "specialization": "Programming",
      "degree": "bgfaedfa",
      "certifications": "adsfadsf",
      "daysAvailable": "45",
      "hoursAvailable": "46",
      "resume": "C:\\fakepath\\shekhar resume 2.0.pdf"
    },
    {
      "id": "e29d",
      "fullName": "shyam",
      "contactNumber": "08868817364",
      "email": "shekharjugtwan2002@gmail.com",
      "experience": 2,
      "teachingDomain": "Computer Science",
      "specialization": "Data Structures",
      "degree": "M Tech - CSE",
      "certifications": " SAP cloud computing",
      "daysAvailable": "45",
      "hoursAvailable": "1024",
      "resume": null
    },
    {
      "id": "ef31",
      "fullName": "",
      "contactNumber": "",
      "email": "",
      "experience": "",
      "teachingDomain": "",
      "specialization": "",
      "degree": "",
      "certifications": "",
      "daysAvailable": "",
      "hoursAvailable": "",
      "resume": null
    }
  ],
"additionalDetails_Candidates": [
    {
      "id": "de7b",
      "username": "khushi",
      "email": "khushi@gmail.com",
      "phoneNumber": "7058175881",
      "location": "Solapur ",
      "companyName": "walchand institute of technology",
      "status": "Studying",
      "specialization": "cse",
      "gender": "Female",
      "password": "khushi@123"
    },
    {
      "id": "2948",
      "username": "arpita",
      "email": "arpita@gmail.com",
      "phoneNumber": "1234567890",
      "location": "Latur",
      "specialization": "cse",
      "companyName": "walchand institue of technology",
      "gender": "Female",
      "status": "Studying",
      "password": "arpita@123"
    },
    {
      "id": "4bc4",
      "username": "ankita",
      "email": "ankita@gmail.com",
      "phoneNumber": "1234567891",
      "location": "mumbai",
      "specialization": "cse",
      "companyName": "infosys",
      "gender": "Female",
      "status": "Working",
      "password": "ankita@123"
    },
    {
      "id": "0",
      "username": "admin",
      "email": "admin@gmail.com",
      "phoneNumber": "1234567800",
      "location": "Chennai",
      "specialization": "IT",
      "companyName": "TCE",
      "gender": "Female",
      "status": "Graduate",
      "password": "Abc@123456"
    }
  ],  
  {
  "test_course": [
    {
      "title": "Introduction to BigData",
      "createdAt": "10-12-24",
      "instructorId": 123,
      "courseId": 542,
      "entrolledCandidates": [],
      "assessment": [
        {
          "assessmentName": "new 3",
          "questions": [
            {
              "question": "weq",
              "choices": [
                "weqw",
                "eqwe",
                "qweqw",
                "weqwqwe"
              ],
              "answer": "weqw"
            }
          ],
          "assessmentID": "bd9df788-97e1-42d3-b918-1aeba025179d",
          "createdAt": "2024-12-22T10:42:52.370Z",
          "schedule": {
            "isScheduled": true,
            "scheduledDetails": {
              "assessmentDate": "2024-12-25",
              "startTime": "09:02",
              "endTime": "23:59"
            }
          },
          "assessmentCompletions": [
            {
              "userId": 1231243,
              "completionDate": "2024-12-25T17:39:19.158Z",
              "assessmentData": {
                "assessmentName": "new 3",
                "createdAt": "2024-12-22T10:42:52.370Z",
                "scheduledDetails": {
                  "assessmentDate": "2024-12-25",
                  "startTime": "09:02",
                  "endTime": "23:59"
                },
                "totalQuestions": 1,
                "questions": [
                  {
                    "question": "weq",
                    "choices": [
                      "weqw",
                      "eqwe",
                      "qweqw",
                      "weqwqwe"
                    ],
                    "answer": "weqw",
                    "userAnswer": "weqwqwe"
                  }
                ],
                "startAt": "2024-12-25T17:39:09.086Z",
                "completionAt": "2024-12-25T17:39:19.158Z"
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "assessmentName": "new 4",
          "questions": [
            {
              "question": "q",
              "choices": [
                "ab",
                "cc",
                "f",
                "t"
              ],
              "answer": "cc"
            },
            {
              "question": "er",
              "choices": [
                "w",
                "re",
                "ee",
                "r"
              ],
              "answer": "ee"
            }
          ],
          "assessmentID": "14ceb3ec-b6fa-4120-bc80-6b872444af88",
          "createdAt": "2024-12-24T12:47:04.983Z",
          "schedule": {
            "isScheduled": true,
            "scheduledDetails": {
              "assessmentDate": "2024-12-28",
              "startTime": "09:21",
              "endTime": "21:25"
            }
          },
          "assessmentCompletions": []
        },
        {
          "assessmentName": "new 5",
          "questions": [
            {
              "question": "weer",
              "choices": [
                "ewrwer",
                "wer",
                "werwer",
                "werwer"
              ],
              "answer": "werwer"
            },
            {
              "question": "werwer",
              "choices": [
                "rwerrerwe",
                "rwer",
                "werwer",
                "werwerwerwer"
              ],
              "answer": "werwerwerwer"
            }
          ],
          "assessmentID": "9ff16807-7108-43b8-8b8d-4f86a7b39d4f",
          "createdAt": "2024-12-24T15:49:58.070Z",
          "schedule": {
            "isScheduled": true,
            "scheduledDetails": {
              "assessmentDate": "2024-12-24",
              "startTime": "22:14",
              "endTime": "23:25"
            }
          },
          "assessmentCompletions": []
        }
      ],
      "id": "8cd5"
    },
    {
      "title": "DevOps for Beginners",
      "createdAt": "12-12-24",
      "instructorId": 123,
      "courseId": 543,
      "assessment": [
        {
          "assessmentName": "assessment 1 in DevOps for Beginners",
          "questions": [
            {
              "question": "wew ? ",
              "choices": [
                "a",
                "b",
                "c",
                "d"
              ],
              "answer": "a"
            }
          ],
          "assessmentID": "d473516c-1381-40cf-947d-8e510ad39395",
          "createdAt": "2024-12-21T17:09:42.415Z",
          "schedule": {
            "isScheduled": true,
            "scheduledDetails": {
              "assessmentDate": "2024-12-24",
              "startTime": "15:00",
              "endTime": "16:00"
            }
          },
          "assessmentCompletions": []
        },
        {
          "assessmentName": "new 2 in dev",
          "questions": [
            {
              "question": "werwer",
              "choices": [
                "werwer",
                "werwe",
                "rewr",
                "werewrewr"
              ],
              "answer": "werewrewr"
            },
            {
              "question": "werer",
              "choices": [
                "rwer",
                "er",
                "wer",
                "rr"
              ],
              "answer": "rr"
            }
          ],
          "assessmentID": "4376138a-47b8-4f43-930d-9d5b81086a06",
          "createdAt": "2024-12-24T15:50:55.517Z",
          "schedule": {
            "isScheduled": true,
            "scheduledDetails": {
              "assessmentDate": "2024-12-26",
              "startTime": "21:22",
              "endTime": "21:26"
            }
          },
          "assessmentCompletions": []
        },
        {
          "assessmentName": "new 3 in dev",
          "questions": [
            {
              "question": "wewe",
              "choices": [
                "r",
                "t",
                "y",
                "u"
              ],
              "answer": "y"
            }
          ],
          "assessmentID": "9d3e78f5-e806-4190-8a39-78ec715e7924",
          "createdAt": "2024-12-24T15:51:10.312Z",
          "schedule": {
            "isScheduled": false,
            "scheduledDetails": ""
          },
          "assessmentCompletions": []
        }
      ],
      "id": "1099"
    }
  ],
  "test_candidates": [
    {
      "name": "sihabutheen",
      "userId": 1231243,
      "entrolledCourses": [
        {
          "title": "Introduction to BigData",
          "createdAt": "10-12-24",
          "instructorId": 123,
          "courseId": 542,
          "entrolled": "12-12-24",
          "assessmentData": [
            {
              "assessmentID": "bd9df788-97e1-42d3-b918-1aeba025179d",
              "completionDate": "2024-12-25T17:39:19.158Z",
              "assessmentData": {
                "assessmentName": "new 3",
                "createdAt": "2024-12-22T10:42:52.370Z",
                "scheduledDetails": {
                  "assessmentDate": "2024-12-25",
                  "startTime": "09:02",
                  "endTime": "23:59"
                },
                "totalQuestions": 1,
                "questions": [
                  {
                    "question": "weq",
                    "choices": [
                      "weqw",
                      "eqwe",
                      "qweqw",
                      "weqwqwe"
                    ],
                    "answer": "weqw",
                    "userAnswer": "weqwqwe"
                  }
                ],
                "startAt": "2024-12-25T17:39:09.086Z",
                "completionAt": "2024-12-25T17:39:19.158Z"
              }
            }
          ]
        },
        {
          "title": "DevOps for Beginners",
          "createdAt": "12-12-24",
          "instructorId": 123542,
          "entrolled": "12-12-24",
          "courseId": 543
        }
      ],
      "id": "e74c"
    },
    {
      "name": "pratham",
      "userId": 126446243,
      "entrolledCourses": [
        {
          "title": "DevOps for Beginners",
          "createdAt": "12-12-24",
          "instructorId": 123542,
          "entrolled": "25-12-24",
          "courseId": 543
        }
      ],
      "id": "6c62"
    }
  ]
}
 }
